# **ANDRES BONILLA**

H2T 2S9, Montreal, QC, Canada 4383659614 Andres94b@gmail.com LinkedIn Github Website



## **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Current Programmer-Analyst AEC student and Mechatronics Engineer looking for an internship in software development to apply my skills, learn from experienced developers, and advance my career. Four years of professional experience programming machinery for the industry, reading documentation and schematics, and automating industrial processes. Solid knowledge of object-oriented Programming, MVC designs and complex equipment.

#### **RELEVANT SKILLS**

- Web: HTML, CSS, PHP, ASP.NET, jQuery, Bootstrap.
- Programming Languages: Java, C++, C#, Python, JavaScript, SQL.
- Tools & Technologies: React, Vue.js, Git, Node.js, Docker, Linux, UML.
- **Development Methodologies**: Agile, Scrum.
- **Personal skills**: Highly adaptable, problem solver, motivated, interpersonal relationships, excellent multilingual verbal and written communicator.

#### **EDUCATION**

**AEC – Information Technology Programmer Analyst**LaSalle College

Sep 2023 – Present Montreal, QC, Canada

**Bachelor's degree in Mechatronics Engineering** University Militar Nueva Granada Jul 2011 – Nov 2017 Bogotá, Colombia

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Technical Service Engineer**

Mar 2017 – Mar 2021 Bogotá, Colombia

Imocom SAS

• Installation and programming of automation and robotics systems for injection molding machines using C++.

- Read electrical, pneumatic, mechanical and hydraulic schematics to provide maintenance of machinery.
- Automation plants using more than 30 different equipment brands and types.

## **Experience Leader**

June 2022 – May 2023

GrowPro Experience

Sydney, Australia

- Using Zoho CRM to track status and handle customer relationships.
- Improving educational and customer experiences by identifying opportunities and responding to requests professionally.

**Server Assistant** 

Nov 2023 - Present

Restaurant L'Orignal

Montreal. QC, Canada

• Communication with kitchen staff and guests, considering dietary needs and preferences.

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English fluent
- French fluent
- Spanish native